（生徒Ａ）でさ〜
（生徒Ｃ）うっそ やだ
- And so, then...
- No way!
（生徒Ａ）
め… 芽亜里(めあり)ちゃん 聞いたよ
Mary! I heard you repaid
your 50 million yen debt
５千万の借金と
ミケを返上したんだってね
and aren't Mittens anymore!
（生徒Ｂ）
さ… さすが芽亜里ちゃん
Way to go, Mary!
（生徒Ｃ）ホント ホント
Really!
（生徒Ａ）あっ あ… あの…
今まで… その…
Well, we're... sorry about how we acted.
ごめんね
（３人）は… あ…
Aw, you know it doesn't bother me.
（芽亜里）うん もう〜
そんなの
気にしてるわけないじゃない
We're friends, right?
私たち 友達でしょ？
That's right.
（生徒Ｂ）そ… そうだよね
Aw, how silly of me.
（生徒Ａ）やだ 私ったら
（４人）アハハハ…
（芽亜里）
ウフフ うん じゃ
またケーキ食べに行こうね！
Let's get some cake again sometime.
（芽亜里）ん？
（鈴井(すずい)）あっ
（芽亜里）別に…
Not really. The school rules say
you have to be mean to house pets.
家畜をいじめ抜くのは
学園のルールだし
あんなもんでしょ
- That's just how it works.
- Really?
そ… そう？
（芽亜里）
家畜が人間に戻るなんて
めったにないからね
House pets almost never go back
to being human.
安心して いじめられるはずが
例外を前にして慌ててるのよ
They thought it was safe to bully me.
Now, they're freaking out.
They're all a bunch of idiots.
ホント バカばっかなんだから
まっ それは それとして…
Anyway, that aside...
私をコケにしてくれた
生徒会は
I'm never forgiving the student council
for what they did to me.
絶対に許さないけどね
あ…
Anyway, about Yumeko...
（芽亜里）
それより夢子(ゆめこ)のことだけど
Did you know?
知ってる？
あいつ せっかく債務整理大集会で
大金 手に入れたのに
She won all that money
at the Debt Settlement Party
借金 返してないって
and hasn't paid it back.
え？
（芽亜里）
大会で 借金を減らせるチャンスが
あったのに
She had a chance to lessen her debts
at the party, and she's wasting it.
それも わざと棒に振ってる
What do you mean?
I don't understand.
（鈴井）どういうこと？
意味が分からない
ミケの座を
あえて手放したくないっていうか
She doesn't want to give up being Mittens.
Or maybe she wants the benefits.
ミケの特典が欲しいってとこかも
ミケに特典なんて… あ！
Being Mittens has benefits?
That's right. Official matches.
（芽亜里）そうよ 公式戦
Don't tell me...
まさか！
夢子は生徒会に
公式戦を挑むつもりなのか？
Yumeko wants to challenge
the student council to a match?
Did Yumeko tell you anything?
（芽亜里）
あんた！
夢子から何か聞いてないの？
What do you mean?
な… 何かって？
ギャンブルなら
ほかに いくらでもやれるのに
There's tons of other ways to gamble.
So, why an official match?
なんで わざわざ公式戦なのよ？
いや 聞いてないけど…
She didn't say anything.
（鈴井）あ！
（芽亜里）何？
What?
（鈴井）そういえば 前に
She did say she wanted to gamble
with the student council president.
生徒会長とギャンブルしたい
って言ってたような…
はあ？
Ryota. Mary.
（夢子）鈴井さん 芽亜里さん
Good morning.
おはようございます
（鈴井）あっ おはよう 夢子
Good morning, Yumeko.
（夢子）
芽亜里さん 考えたんですけど
Mary, I've been thinking, and it's not
right for me to take that money I earned
大集会で手に入れたお金
やっぱり 私が頂くわけには
いかないかと…
at the Debt Settlement Party.
It's fine.
別に…
私も借金返済で
１千万だけ使わせてもらったし
I used ten million of it
to pay back my debts.
でも
２人で協力して得たものですし
But we won it by working together.
I don't want to owe you anything.
あんたに借りを
作りたくないんだよ
分 か れ よ！
Take the hint!
あ… はあ
Okay. Then I'll take you up on that offer.
では お言葉に甘えて
（芽亜里）
あ〜 あ〜 持ってけ 持ってけ！
Just take it.
〜
（豆生田(まにゅうだ)）蛇喰(じゃばみ)夢子の人生計画表を
You're not rescinding
Yumeko Jabami's life plan?
取り下げない？
Yes, that's the president's wish.
（清華(さやか)）はい 会長のご意向です
What's going on here?
どういうことだ？
ヤツは大集会で
She got 260 million yen in the party.
２億６千万もの金を
手に入れたはずだ
We're just ignoring that?
それを放っておくのか？
I couldn't say.
（清華）
さて 私には
会長のお心は分かりません
I can't say what's on her mind.
ただ 会長のご指示で
蛇喰夢子の身辺調査をしたところ
But when I looked into Yumeko Jabami
at her request,
彼女は かなりの資産を
持っていることが分かりました
I found that she has considerable
reserves of funds.
What?
なに！
蛇喰夢子は１人暮らし
Yumeko Jabami lives alone.
Her parents have passed away. Her only
immediate relative is an older sister.
両親は他界しており
家族は姉が１人いるのみです
この姉が長期にわたり
She's spent a long time in the special
ward of a university hospital,
大学病院の特別病棟に
入院しており
その費用は
全て彼女が負担しています
which is paid for by Yumeko.
相当の資金がなければ
説明がつきません
That can only be explained
by a large bank account.
（百合子(ゆりこ)）
その気になれば返せる借金を
So, she's not paying back debts
she could pay?
返さないということでしょうか？
What is she thinking?
どういう意図があるのでしょう？
（るな）
ニャハ！
そんなの決まってんじゃん！
What else?
The official match.
公式戦だよ
夢子は会長と
Yumeko says she wants to gamble
with the president. That scared me.
ギャンブル
したいんだって！
（妄(みだり)）ぐあ！
（るな）わっ びっくりした！
（るな）どしたの 妄ちゃん？
What's wrong, Midari?
夢子が会長と公式戦だと？
Yumeko, having an official match
with the president?
マズい… 会長に壊される
That's bad! The president will kill her.
No!
ダメだ！
ダメだ ダメだ ダメだ ダメだ…
あれは私のもの！
- She belongs to me!
- Hey! Ikishima!
（豆生田）おい 生志摩(いきしま)！
（ドアの開閉音）
ふん 何だ あいつは？
What's her problem?
（るな）ニャハ
気をつけてね〜
妄ちゃん
Be careful, Midari.
（鐘の音）
CLASSICS B
あっ
Class is finally over, huh?
やっと授業が終わりましたね
待ちきれなくて
うわの空になってしまいました
I was so eager for this to begin
that I wasn't paying attention. Let's go.
さあ 参りましょう
（鈴井）
えっと それって まさか公式戦？
Um... do you mean the official match?
（夢子）ええ もちろん
Yes, of course.
（鈴井）
あの もう少し
準備とかしたほうが…
Shouldn't you take more time to get ready?
（夢子）
心の準備なら
とうに終わってますから
My heart's been ready a long time.
Don't worry.
大丈夫です
（鈴井）いや そうじゃなくて…
No, that's not what I mean.
（鈴井）
一度 負かされた会長に
また挑もうなんて
The student council president
beat her once.
一体 何が 夢子を
そうさせるんだろう
She's going to try again?
What's making Yumeko do this?
ハア
分かった
Fine. I think we just have to go
to the student council room.
生徒会室に行けば
申し込めると思う
案内するよ
- I'll take you there.
- Thanks.
（夢子）ありがとうございます！
An official match
with the student council president, huh?
（芽亜里）
生徒会長との公式戦… ね
まあ あの２億は
あぶく銭みたいなもんだし
Well, 200 million isn't a lot of money.
好きにしろって感じだけど…
- She can do what she wants with it.
- Mary, let's go home together.
芽亜里ちゃん 一緒に帰ろう
- What do you want to do?
- What do I do?
（芽亜里）
私は どうする
This is the student council's system.
I'm winning and losing inside that system.
生徒会の作った仕組みの中で
勝っただの 負けただの
When I think about
how they're in control of me,
いいようにされていると思うと
頭に血が上って吐き気がする
blood rushes to my head
and I want to vomit.
Am I okay with this?
このままでいいのか？
あっ
（綺羅莉(きらり)）早乙女(さおとめ)芽亜里さん
Mary Saotome,
how about you join me for a cup of tea?
よかったら お茶でもどうかしら？
２人きりで
Just the two of us.
THE INVITING GIRL
（妄）ウヘッ 見つけたぜ〜 夢子
I found you, Yumeko!
I remember you.
あなたは あのときの…
その節は お世話になりました
Thank you so much for your help.
夢子
Yumeko, I heard you haven't paid
back the 310 million you owe.
お前 ３億１千万の借金
まだ返してねえらしいじゃねえか
As beautification officer,
I can't ignore that.
美化委員長として 見逃せねえな〜
わっ
なっ いきなり何すんだよ！
What are you doing?
I reform the garbage in the school,
beautifying it into its proper form.
校内のゴミを矯正し
あるべき姿に美化する
それが美化委員の役割だ
That's my job.
The Beautification Committee
is one of the organizations
逮捕権限を持つ
数少ない組織のひとつなんだよ
- with the power to arrest.
- Wait--
連れてけ！
- Take her.
- Okay!
（部下たち）は〜い
いろいろ取り調べてやんなきゃ
いけないからな
I have lots of things to ask her,
lots of things.
たっぷりと
（鈴井）いや 逮捕って 急に…
Arrest? You can't just--
Take him while you're at it.
（妄）
ついでだ
この男も連れてけ！
- Okay.
（部下たち）は〜い
（鈴井）え？
ぶっ！
うわっ あ…
（妄）
ウヘッ そんな顔するなよ 夢子
Don't make that face, Yumeko.
Here.
ほらよ
一体 何のご用ですか？
What do you want? I have plans.
このあと 予定があるのですが！
Plans, huh?
予定ねえ　知ってるよ
I know.
お前みたいな不良生徒が
会長様に会えると思ってんのか？
Do you think a delinquent like you
will be allowed to meet the president?
まして公式戦なんて論外だ
And an official match
is out of the question.
もし どうしても
If you insist...
If you absolutely insist
on challenging her,
どうしても会長と
やりたいって言うんなら
gamble with me first, Yumeko.
まず あたしとギャンブルしようぜ
夢子？
Oh, you want to gamble.
（夢子）まあ ギャンブル！
Well, why didn't you say so?
それならそうと
早く言ってくださればよかったのに
So, what are we doing?
で 何をやるんですか？
フッ ウフフ
I believed you'd say that.
お前なら
そう言ってくれると思ってたぜ
I can tell. You and I are the same.
あたしには分かる
あたしとお前は同類
Perverts who get off on the thrill!
スリルに興奮するド変態だ！
Oh, no, a pervert? How lewd.
そんな…
ド変態だなんて はしたない
（鈴井）え〜！
（妄）さて
Now, this place is an interrogation room,
created to reform the school's garbage.
ここは学園のゴミどもを
矯正するために地下に造られた—
取調施設だ
It's split into an interrogation room
and an observation room.
直接 尋問するための聴取室と
別室で観察するための
監視室に分かれている
どちらも完全防音の密室で
２つの部屋をつなぐのは
Both of them are locked and sealed
and completely soundproof.
Only the monitors and cameras
in both connect the two.
それぞれに設置された
カメラとモニターだけだ
We call it the ESP game.
あたしたちは
“ＥＳＰ(イーエスピー)ゲーム”って呼んでる
ルールは簡単
The rules are simple.
It's a card guessing game.
別室にいるディーラーが
You guess how the dealer in another room
will line up cards. Here's how it works.
どうカードを並べるか予想する
カード当てゲームだ
具体的な手順としては
First, the dealer lays out the cards.
まず ディーラーが
カードを好きな順に並べる
ディーラーの手元は
モニターを通して見ることができる
You can see the area in front of them
via the monitors.
ディーラーが並べ終えたら
今度は あたしたちが並べる
Once the dealer lays out the cards,
we lay out our own.
終わったら ３人ともオープンだ
Then all three of us reveal our hands.
ディーラーの並べ方に
合致する枚数の多いほうが勝ち
The one whose cards match
the dealers most often wins.
They win one point for every correct card.
枚数差がポイントになる
I see. Nice and simple.
How much shall we bet?
なるほど シンプルでいいですね
賭け金は どうしましょう？
夢子よ
ちげえだろ！
Yumeko, that's not how we do it.
Don't you even dare.
ふざけんじゃねえぞ
金の取り合いなんて
ヌルいことやってらんねえだろ？
We're not going to waste our time
with something as stupid as money.
ゲームの勝者は
The winner of the game
pulls the trigger once for every win.
勝ち点の分だけ
引き金を引くんだよ！
You can put in as many bullets as you like
and spin the chamber.
この銃に
好きな数の弾を込め
弾倉を回す
装填(そうてん)できる弾は 最大６発
The maximum you can load it with
is six bullets.
You can put a bullet in every chamber,
or not a single one.
全て込めてもいいし
１発も込めなくてもいい
終わったら
２丁ともシューターに入れて
Once that's done, we each conceal our gun
so that you can't tell the difference.
区別がつかないようにする
そこから勝ったほうが１丁取って
The winner takes one gun and pulls
the trigger once for every victory.
相手に向かって
勝ち点の分だけ引き金を引く
Whoever gets hit
with a single bullet loses!
１発でも
弾が当たったほうの負けだ
ウフ アハッ どうよ！
なかなか面白れえだろ？
Well? Fun game, huh?
Um, that's an air gun or something, rig--
あ… あの それって
もちろん エアガンか何か…
（バン）
うわ！
ウヘッ
分かったらやるぞ 夢子
Got it? Let's get started, Yumeko.
You're the only one I can count on.
お前だけが頼りなんだよ
最高の読み合い
殺し合いをしようぜ
Let's have the best game
and the best killing.
安心しろよ
Don't worry.
１発じゃ そうそう死ぬことはねえ
You don't usually die from one shot.
すぐに病院にも
連れてってやるしよ
And I'll take you right to a hospital!
あ… もしかして
Or maybe you're worried
about what will happen if you kill me?
あたしを殺しちまったときのことを
心配してんのか？
バッカ 大丈夫だよ
You idiot! Don't worry!
The president will take care of it.
あとのことは
会長が何とかしてくれる！
A shooting in the school
would ruin our reputation after all.
校内で銃撃事件なんて
評判が
ガタ落ちどころじゃねえからな！
絶対に世間にバレねえように
してくれるって
She'll make sure nobody finds out.
お前は何も心配しなくていい
You don't even have to worry
about a thing. Let's have a great time!
心ゆくまで 楽しもうぜ〜！
Is she crazy?
あ… 頭 おかしいのか？
帰ろう 夢子！
Let's go, Yumeko. There's no need to...
こんなヤツにつきあう必要…
ぐっ！
（妄）なあ お前…
Hey, you.
Why are you trying to wreck our fun?
何だって
あたしたちの楽しみを止めるんだ？
会長もしてくれない
The student council president won't
do this with me. Yumeko's all I've got.
夢子しかいないんだ
は？
お願いだよ やらせてくれよ
Please.
Let me do it.
I can't take it anymore.
もう 我慢できない
あ… 頭がおかしくなっちまう！
I'm going crazy!
You're insane! Let us out!
ふざけるな！
いいから ここから出してくれ！
Why? I'm begging you!
なんでだよ〜
こんなに頼んでるのに
This game is insane. We won't do it,
no matter how much you beg!
こんな狂ったギャンブル
どれだけ頼まれたって
やるわけがない！
くっ… 分かった 分かったよ
Fine.
You're in the way.
お前 邪魔だ
うっ！
Now, now. Calm down.
（夢子）
まあ まあ 落ち着いてください
私は やらないなんて
ひと言も言ってないですよ
I didn't say a thing about not playing.
（鈴井）ゆ… 夢子
Yumeko...
ギャンブルとしては
即物的すぎる嫌いはありますが
It seems a little primitive
for a game of chance.
そこまでおっしゃるなら
しかたありません
But if you're that insistent
then I have no choice. I accept.
お受けしましょう
What are you talking about?
You can't possibly...
な… 何 言ってんだよ！
こんなギャンブル
いくら何… で… も…
はあ
（鈴井）
う… うそだろ
You're kidding me.
It's like you're...
それじゃあ まるで…
（妄･夢子）はあ〜
you're the same!
（鈴井）
同類じゃないか！
（２人）フフフ…
（綺羅莉）
これはセイロン島のディンブラ
華やかな香りね
This is Ceylon Dimbula tea.
It smells wonderful, doesn't it?
I hope you like it.
口に合うとよいのだけれど
大集会 楽しませてもらったわ
I enjoyed the party.
実際に 億単位の金を
かすめ取られたのは
You're the first to win from us an amount
in the hundreds of millions of yen.
あなたたちが初めてよ
Normally, people don't notice the loophole
in the debt swapping rules.
普通は 借金付け替えの
ルールの穴に気付かないし
And even if someone does,
they're happy to skim some pocket change.
たまに気付いても
小銭を稼いで
満足する者ばかり
つまらないわ
It's boring. You gave up the title
of Mittens and paid off your debts, right?
あなた 借金もミケも
返上したのね
これじゃ
あなたのための人生計画表を
We'll have to get rid of the life plan
we created for you.
破棄せざるをえない
フフッ 大損害ね
That's a huge loss.
（芽亜里）
だ… だったら
何だって言うんですか！
So, what? That's just something
you tried to force on me.
あれは あなた方が
一方的に押しつけてきただけで…
Well, it doesn't matter.
（綺羅莉）
まあ そんなことは
どうでもいいのよ
芽亜里
Mary.
あなた
Join the student council.
生徒会に入りなさい
あ？
I have three conditions
for accepting this game.
（夢子）
このギャンブル お受けするには
３点ほど条件があります
Three games maximum.
ゲームは
最大３セットまでとすること
ディーラーは
鈴井さんにやっていただくこと
Ryota will be the dealer.
（鈴井）え!?
（夢子）そして…
And the loser must pay one billion yen
to the winner.
敗者は勝者に
10億円を支払うこと
（妄）
ウヘッ 状況 理解してんのかよ？
Do you understand the situation?
なんで お前が条件出すんだよ
Why are you setting conditions for me?
アハハハッ ったく 狂ってやがる
You're crazy.
アハハッ ハッ ハハハハ！
Hmm... One billion, huh?
そうだな 10億ねえ
それはいい
That's fine, I don't care about money.
あたしは金なんて
どうだっていいからな
この鈴井？ とかいう男が
ディーラーってのも かまわねえ
And I don't care if this... Ryota
is the dealer.
You're suspicious that I'll cheat, right?
イカサマを疑ってんだろ？
でもよ〜
But...
Why only three games?
３セットまでってのは
どうゆうことだ？
てめえ まさか 引き分け
狙ってんじゃねえだろうな？
You're not trying to set up a tie, right?
カード並べに全て勝ち
Winning all the card games,
and then missing every shot?
わざと弾を外せばいいなんて
思ってねえだろうな〜！
I couldn't say.
さて…
（妄）ウヘッ いいぜ
Fine! A girl like you would never
show me a boring game.
お前ほどのタマが
つまんねえゲームを
するわきゃねえよな〜
あたしは信じてるぜ
I believe in you.
But I need insurance.
ただ 保険はいるな
ルール追加だ
I'm adding a rule. Every missed shot means
your opponent can take one shot at you.
弾を外したら
その分 相手に撃たれる
それなら３回でいいぞ
- If you agree, three games is fine.
- Yes, that's fine.
ええ かまいませんよ
Okay, let's get started.
よし 始めるぞ
What? But then even if you win,
you can't deliberately miss.
そんな…
それじゃ
カード当てに勝っても
弾をわざと
外すことはできない
One of you is going to be shot.
どちらかが
撃たれることは確実！
Ryota, we're going to the monitoring room.
（部下Ａ）
鈴井〜 さっさと監視室に行くよ！
（夢子）ウフフ
鈴井さんが ディーラーを
してくださるなら安心です
If you're the dealer,
then I don't have to worry.
（鈴井）
そんな… 買いかぶりだ
She's putting too much faith in me.
俺の並べるカードしだいで
夢子の命が！
Depending on the cards I lay out,
Yumeko might die.
うっ！
（夢子）鈴井さん
Ryota...
大丈夫ですよ
it's okay.
だって 私たちには
Remember, we've got "it."
アレがあるでは
ありませんか アレが
（鈴井）は？
アレをサインにすれば
必ず勝てます
- If we use "it" as a sign, we can win.
- That's the spirit, Yumeko!
ウヘッ その意気だよ 夢子！
Okay, Ryota.
それでは鈴井さん またあとで
See you later.
（鈴井）うん…
Yeah.
ウヘッ サイン？
Sign? Can you tell what cards he's got
just by looking at his hands?
手元だけで
カードの中身を伝えられるのか？
気をつけねえとな〜
I'd better be careful.
（部下Ｂ）
はい これがＥＳＰカードね
Okay, here are the ESP cards.
Line them up in the rectangle
so the camera can see.
（部下Ａ）
机の枠線内に
カメラに映るように並べて
（部下Ｂ）
手とカード以外のものを映すのは
禁止だよ
Don't show anything
but your hands and the card.
（鈴井）
このゲームで 僕がいちばん
気をつけなきゃいけないのは
The thing I have to be most careful
about here is cheating,
イカサマ
カードの順番を
生志摩に知られることだ
Ikishima knowing
what order the cards are in.
今のところ
Right now, I'm not seeing anything
that would suggest cheating.
イカサマを疑わせるようなものは
何もない
あとは並べる順番をどうするかだ
The next question is how I line them up.
The problem is...
問題は…
アレをサインにすれば
必ず勝てます
If we use "it" as a sign, we can win.
If we use "it" as a sign...
アレをサインにすれば
アレをサインにすれば…
（鈴井）
アレって…
What is "it"?
何だ!?
（芽亜里）冗談は よしてください
That's not funny.
Why would I join the student council?
なんで私を生徒会に…
（綺羅莉）あら 私は本気よ
I'm serious. The talents that made you
capable of stealing 310 million yen
生徒会から ３億１千万円
かすめ取ったその手腕
from the student council...
その才能…
私が
I'm telling you
that you're worthy of the job.
あなたは生徒会にふさわしいと
言っているのよ
（芽亜里）無理ですって
It's impossible.
（綺羅莉）それは つまり
Do you mean that you're refusing a request
from me, the student council president?
生徒会長である私の誘いを
断るということ？
（芽亜里）ん… あっ
（綺羅莉）どうしてかしら？
Why is that?
You should know very well the advantages
of being a member of the student council.
生徒会役員であることの利得は
あなたなら重々 分かっているはず
なのに どうして？
So, why? Are you scared
of the other members?
ほかの役員が怖いの？
だとしたら 生徒会に
ばく大な損害を与えたのはなぜ？
Then why inflict such a massive loss
on the student council?
私のことを
疑っている？
Or are you suspicious of me?
Then just say you'll think about it.
なら保留すればいい
頭から拒絶するのは
得策ではないでしょ？
It's not smart to just refuse
outright, is it?
どうして？
Why? I'm asking you a question.
ねえ 聞いてるのよ
（芽亜里）あ…
Oh, sorry.
（綺羅莉）ああ ごめんなさい
あなたの行動が
みじんも理解できないものだから…
I can't understand
how you're thinking in the slightest.
私 あなたのような理解できない人
People like you who I can't understand...
大好きなの
I love them.
（部下Ｂ）鈴井 早く始めなよ
Ryota, hurry up.
考えたってムダだって
There's no point in thinking about it.
Maybe...
（鈴井）
かもしれない
こんな大役
I was a house pet until just a while ago.
I can't do this.
つい この間まで家畜だった僕に
務まるわけない
家畜を返上できたのだって
自分の力じゃない
It wasn't my own power that freed me
either. It was thanks to Yumeko.
夢子のおかげだ
そうだ！
That's right.
That's why I have to do this.
だからこそ
僕がやらなきゃいけないんだ
夢子は僕を助けてくれた
Yumeko saved me.
So, now, it's my turn.
だったら次は 僕の番だ！
考えろ
夢子のために何ができるか
Think. What can you do for Yumeko?
Think! As hard as you can!
考えるんだ！ 死ぬ気で！
あっ 覚悟を決めたらしいぜ
Looks like he's ready.
（鈴井）
夢子の目的は
Yumeko's goal is to make Ikishima think
we have a sign we can share
僕たちにはサインがあるから
カード当ては必ず勝てる
so that she can win.
そう生志摩に思い込ませることだ
必ず負ける勝負で
弾を込めるはずがない
If she knows she'll lose,
she won't use any bullets.
つまり生志摩は
サインの意味を見破るまで
Ikishima can't put in bullets
until she knows what the sign is.
弾を込められない
僕の読みが当たってるなら
サインは何でもいい
If I'm right, the sign doesn't matter.
What's important is the fact
that I'm sending a sign.
サインを送ること自体が
重要なんだ！
（妄）２？ それともチョキか？
Two? Or scissors?
さて どういう意味が
あるのかねえ？
What does that mean, I wonder?
（夢子）こちら側の映像は
Can Ryota see what's going on our side?
鈴井さんのいる部屋に
映っているのですか？
（妄）ああ 声は聞こえねえが
Yeah. He can't hear us. But he can see
everything, not just the hands.
向こうと違って
こっちは 手元以外も映ってるぞ
（夢子）ウッフフ
なるほど よく分かりました
I see. I understand.
Okay. First, load the bullets.
（妄）よし まず弾を込めろ
う〜ん
夢子よ〜
Yumeko, you don't need to say
how many bullets you put in.
何発込めたか 申告する必要はねえ
が… ひとつ教えといてやるよ
But I'll tell you one thing.
あたしは ６発込める
I'm putting in six!
え!?
（鈴井）
い… 今…
Ikishima just put six bullets in, right?
生志摩は 確かに６発入れたよな？
バ… バカな！
Is she stupid?
もし こちらにサインがあれば
自殺行為じゃないか！
If we do have a sign, that's suicide.
Does she know the sign is a bluff?
まさか サインがブラフだと
バレてるのか？
（妄）ギャハ いよいよだな
It's finally time for a card game
where you bet your life!
命を賭けたカード並べだ！
You're ready, right?
覚悟はいいな？
ええ
Yes.
ああ…
（バイブ音）
（妄）
よし 開かせろ
- Okay, have him show the cards.
- Okay.
は〜い
Ryota, show the cards.
鈴井 カード開いて
（鈴井）
もう祈るしかない　頼む！
I'll just have to pray.
Please...
ウヘヘヘ
たまんねえな この瞬間！
I love this moment!
よし いくぞ　オープンだ！
Okay, here we go. Show your hand.
ヌハ〜
う…
はっ
はっ あっ
ああ… はっ
Ikishima got three cards.
生志摩… ３枚
Yumeko got two.
夢子… ２枚
夢子の… 負け
Yumeko... lost!
ウヘッ 何だよ
What? So, the sign was a bluff.
サインはハッタリかよ
まあ いい
It doesn't matter. You're ready, right?
覚悟はできている だったよな？
ウヘッ 夢子よ〜
Yumeko...
見苦しい姿を見せんじゃねえぞ
Don't let me see you embarrass yourself.
ウヘヘ
ハア ハア ハア ハア…
（夢子）生志摩さん
Ikishima, I don't recommend
pulling the trigger on that gun.
その銃の引き金を引くのは
お勧めしません
（妄）あ？
（カチッ）
〜
- Ever see the other side of the moon?
- That's cheating!
（綺羅莉）
月の裏側って見たことある？
（妄）
撃っちまう恐怖は ねえのかよ
- You're not scared to fire?
- Stop insulting me.
（夢子）
バカにするのも
大概にしてくださいね
（綺羅莉）
いずれ 殺してあげるわ
- Someday, I'll kill you.
- Student Council President!
（清華）
会長！
EPISODE 7: THE GIRLS THAT REFUSE
（芽亜里）
さようなら
Goodbye.